A Guide to the Chesapeake and Ohio Railway Company Records, 1836-1943
Library of Virginia
- Series I. Maps, 1836-1943., Extent: 196 maps.
  - Richmond Dock & Vicinity from 13th St. to Ship Locks. F. B. Isaacs, Eng., W. P. May 1901., Dimensions: each 15 x 23 in.; Scale: 100 ft. to 1 in.; Media: Manuscript map on linen paper.; Sheets: 3. (Othertype 755.44 R15 1901 (1))
  - Richmond Dock & Vicinity from 17th St. to Ship Locks. F. B. Isaacs, W. P. May 1901., Dimensions: each 17.5 x 24 in.; Scale: 100 ft. to 1 in.; Media: Manuscript map on linen paper.; Sheets: 2. (Othertype 755.44 R15 1901 (2))
  - Map of Property between 17th & 18th and Broad & Clay Sts., Richmond, Va. C. & O. Ry. Jan. 1907., Dimensions: 21 x 20.5 in.; Scale: 30 ft. to 1 in.; Media: Manuscript map on linen paper. Colored.; Sheets: 1. (Othertype 755.44 R15 1907)
  - [Map of the Richmond Dock and vicinity, showing Chesapeake and Ohio and Southern Railway tracks]. n.d.., Dimensions: each 16 x 30 in.; Scale: Scale not given.; Media: Manuscript map. Colored.; Sheets: 2. (Othertype 755.44 R15 n.d.)
  - [Map of railroad right of way, Richmond City, between 29th Street and Orleans Street]. n.d.., Dimensions: 19 x 27 in.; Scale: Scale not given.; Media: Manuscript map on linen paper. Colored.; Sheets: 1. (Othertype 755.44 R15 n.d. (1))
  - [Vicinity of 9th and Canal Streets, Richmond, Va.]. n.d.., Dimensions: 7 x 24.5 in.; Scale: Scale not given.; Media: Manuscript sketch map on linen paper.; Sheets: 1. (Othertype 755.44 R15 n.d. (2))
  - [Vicinity of 9th and Canal Streets, Richmond, Va.]. n.d.., Dimensions: 17 x 25.5 in.; Scale: Scale not given.; Media: Manuscript sketch map.; Sheets: 1. (Othertype 755.44 R15 n.d. (3))
  - Map showing Harbor Lines, and Dyke Line, and Property Owners, between Ship Lock and Shockoe Creek. n.d.., Dimensions: each 33 x 20.5 in.; Scale: 100 ft. to 1 in.; Media: Blueprint; Sheets: 3. (Othertype 755.44 R15 n.d. (4))
  - Plat of Mansfield [Richmond City, showing right of way of Virginia Central Railroad]. [Later copy of plat dated July 15, 1859]. n.d.., Dimensions: 18 x 16 in.; Scale: Scale not given.; Media: Manuscript plat on linen paper.; Sheets: 1. (Othertype 755.44 S8 [1859] n.d.)
  - Plat showing property lines between Potter and Balding Sts. and changes in Shockoe Creek, Richmond, Va. Dec. 13, 1905., Dimensions: 24 x 41 in.; Scale: 50 ft. to 1 in.; Media: Manuscript map on linen paper.; Sheets: 1. (Othertype 755.44 S8 1905)
  - Plat and profile of North Anna Branch Line [Hanover County]. n.d.., Dimensions: 18.5 x 38 in.; Scale: 300 ft. to 1 in.; Media: Manuscript map on linen paper. Colored.; Sheets: 1. (Othertype 755.45 R15 n.d.)
  - Map of Atlee's Station [Hanover County]. 1873., Dimensions: 9.5 x 27 in.; Scale: 100 ft. to 1 in.; Media: Manuscript plat on linen paper. Colored.; Sheets: 1. (Othertype 755.45 S8 1873 (1))
  - Map of Green Spring Station [Louisa County]. Ches. and Ohio R. R. J. S. Wood. 1874., Dimensions: 10 x 27 in.; Scale: Scale not given.; Media: Manuscript map.; Sheets: 1. (Othertype 755.452 R15 1874)
  - Louisa C[ourt] H[ouse]. M. A. Miller. 1883., Dimensions: 21.5 x 33 in.; Scale: 100 ft. to 1 in.; Media: Manuscript map.; Sheets: 1. (Othertype 755.452 R15 1883)
  - Trevilians Station [Louisa County]. C. & O. R. R. Co. property tinted red. Property conveyed by C. Danne, ex. als., tinted green. n.d.., Dimensions: l2.5 x 17.5 in.; Scale: 200 ft. to 1 in.; Media: Manuscript map. Colored.; Sheets: 1. (Othertype 755.452 R15 n.d.)
  - Map of Bumpass Station [Louisa County.] C & 0 RR. 1873., Dimensions: 22 x 24 in.; Scale: 20 ft. to 1 in.; Media: Manuscript map. Colored.; Sheets: 1. (Othertype 755.452 S8 1873)
  - Pendleton Station [Louisa County]. Showing location of 1 Acre of Land given to the C. & O. R. R. Co. by Dr. P. B. Pendleton. [Contains note added 5/10/1915]. n.d.., Dimensions: 13.5 x 27 in.; Scale: 100 ft. to 1 in.; Media: Manuscript plat. Colored.; Sheets: 1. (Othertype 755.452 S8 n.d. [1915])
  - Partial Plat of Land condemned from Joseph Bruce for Rivanna Connection Canal just above Connection Locks at Columbia, Va. F. B. Isaacs, A. E. May 1898., Dimensions: 13 x 14 in.; Scale: 50 ft. to 1 in.; Media: Manuscript plat on linen paper.; Sheets: 1. (Othertype 758.454 S8 1898)
  - Preliminary Line from Cobham to 1/2 mile East of Campbell, North side of Main Line [Albemarle County]. Barnett. October 1893., imensions: each 17.5 x 23.5 in.; Scale: Scale not given.; Media: Manuscript map. Colored.; Sheets: 3. (Othertype 758.47 R15 1893)
  - Preliminary Survey. From Cobham to 1/2 Mile East of Campbell on North Side of Main Line, C. & O. Ry. Survey of Main Line C. & O. Ry. from 1 Mile East of Cobham to Keswick. [1893?]., Dimensions: Parts 1 and 2, 12 x 23 in. Parts 3-5, 12 x 29 in.; Scale: Scale not given.; Media: Manuscript profile. Colored.; Sheets: 5. (Othertype 755.47 R15 1893?)
  - Alberene Branch [Albemarle County]. n.d.., Dimensions: each 27 x 40 in.; Scale: Scale not given.; Media: Manuscript map. Colored.; Sheets: 5. (Othertype 755.47 R15 n.d. (1))
  - Albemarle Co. [Brookvilie Tunnel to Nelson County line]. Reduced from Original Location Maps of 1852. H. Jacob. Jan. 1885., Dimensions: each 22 x 20 in.; Scale: 200 ft to 1 in.; Media: Manuscript map. Colored.; Sheets: 10. (Othertype 758.47 S8 1852 1885)
  - [Plat showing land required by railroad along right of way in Charlottesville, Albemarle County]. July 19, 1878., Dimensions: 15 x 37 in.; Scale: 100 ft. to 1 in.; Media: Manuscript map on linen paper. colored.; Sheets: 1. (Othertype 755.47 S8 1878)
  - [Map of right of way from Louisa-Albemarle County line to Mechum's River]. M. A. Miller. 1879., Dimensions: each 25 x 40.5 in.; Scale: 200 ft. to 1 in.; Media: Manuscript plats. Colored.; Sheets: 23. (Othertype 755.47 S8 1879)
  - Land at Cobham [Albemarle County]. F. H. Quinby. Sept. 14, 1885., Dimensions: 15 x 27 in.; Scale: 30 ft. to 1 in.; Media: Manuscript plat. Colored.; Sheets: 1. (Othertype 755.47 S8 1885)
  - Right of Way and Track Map. The Chesapeake and Ohio Railway Company. Main Line. June 30, 1916., Dimensions: each 24 x 18 in.; Scale: 200 ft. to 1 in.; Media: Blueline print.; Sheets: 8 numbered 103 through 109,including a supplemental sheet, in 24 parts. (Sheets numbered 1 through 102 and 110 through 178 missing). (Othertype 755.47 S8 1916)
  - Map of Rock Quarry and Spring purchased of T. J. Randolph [Albemarle County]. n.d.., Dimensions: 15.75 x 20.75 in.; Scale: Scale not indicated.; Media: Manuscript plat. Colored.; Sheets: 1. (Othertype 755.47 S8 n.d.)
  - [Plat of right of way through Shadwell and Jefferson farms, Albemarle County, along Rivanna River, also showing Rivanna Canal]. n.d.., Dimensions: 15 x 29 in.; Scale: 200 ft. to 1 in.; Media: Manuscript map on linen paper. Colored.; Sheets: 1. (Othertype 755.47 S8 n.d. (1))
  - Map of Land Owned by the Ches. & Ohio R. R. in Charlottesville. n.d.., Dimensions: each 15.5 x 28 in.; Scale: 100 ft. to 1 in.; Media: Manuscript plat on linen paper. Colored.; Sheets: 2. (Othertype 755.47 S8 n.d. (2))
  - [Map showing railroad right of way through Charlottesville, Virginia]. M. I. Miller's Maps. n.d., Dimensions: each 24 x 39 in.; Scale: 100 ft. to 1 in.; Media: Manuscript map. Colored.; Sheets: 3. (Othertype 755.47 S8 n.d. (3))
  - [Part of Charlottesville showing junction of Chesapeake and Ohio Railroad, Virginia Midland Railroad, and Charlottesville and Rapidan Railroad]. n.d.., Dimensions: 22 x 41 in.; Scale: 50 ft. to 1 in.; Media: Manuscript plat. Colored.; Sheets: 1. (Othertype 755.47 S8 n.d. (4))
  - Plot of that part of N. F. Cabell's Land condemned for the use of t he James Riv. and Kanawha Co. [Nelson County]. 1836., Dimensions: 23 x 18 in.; Scale: 400 ft. to 1 in.; Media: Manuscript map.; Sheets: 1. (Othertype 755.48 C2 1836)
  - Plot of that part of J. C. Cabell's Land condemned for the use of the James Riv. & Kanawha Compy. [Nelson County?]. J. H. Brown. 1836., Dimensions: 18 x 23 in.; Scale: 300 ft. to 1 in.; Media: Manuscript map.; Sheets: 1. (Othertype 755.48 C2 1836 (1))
  - A Map Showing the quantity of Land of Mayo Cabe11 Required for the James River and Kanawha Canal [Nelson County?]. [1836?]., Dimensions: 18 x 23 in.; Scale: Scale not given.; Media: Manuscript map.; Sheets: 1. (Othertype 755.48 C2 [1836?])
  - A Map Showing the quantity of land of James T. Smith required for the James River and Kanawha Canal [Nelson County?]. [1836?]., Dimensions: 18 x 23 in.; Scale: 300 ft. to 1 in.; Media: Manuscript. map.; Sheets: 1. (Othertype 755.48 C2 [1836?] (1))
  - A Map Showing the quantity of Land of Daniel Higginbotham Required for the James River and Kanawha Canal [Nelson County]. [1836?]., Dimensions: 18 x 23 in.; Scale: Scale not given.; Media: Manuscript map.; Sheets: 1. (Othertype 755.48 C2 [1836?] (2))
  - Map of the James River and Kanawha Canal Through the land of Fredrick M. Cabell [Nelson County]. [1836?]., Dimensions: 20 x 28 in.; Scale: 400 ft. to 1 in.; Media: Manuscript map. Colored.; Sheets: 1. (Othertype 755.48 C2 [1836?] (3))
  - Map of the James River and Kanawha Canal as it passes thro' the land of F. W. S. Turner [Nelson County]. [1836?]., Dimensions: 17.5 x 24.5 in.; Scale: 100 ft. to 1 in.; Media: Manuscript map. Colored.; Sheets: 1. (Othertype 755.48 C2 [1836?] (4))
  - A Map Showing the quantity of Land of Joseph C. Cabell [Nelson County]. Required for the James River and Kanawha Canal. [1836?]., Dimensions: 18 x 22 in.; Scale: Scale not given.; Media: Manuscript map.; Sheets: 1. (Othertype 755.48 C2 [1836?] (5))
  - Plot of that part of F. W. S. Turner's Land [Nelson County] Condemned for the use of the James River and Kanawha [Company]. [1836?]., Dimensions: 15 x 21.5 in.; Scale: Scale not given.; Media: Manuscript map.; Sheets: 1. (Othertype 755.48 C2 [1836?] (6))
  - [Plat of lands along right of way, Nelson Co.] Plotted from Condemnation Papers dated October 12th 1836 and June 23rd 1843. James River & Kanawha Co. versus John Horsley, Dec'd & Robert Y. Horsley, respectively. F. B. Isaacs, A. E. C. & O. Ry. Co. April 1897., Dimensions: 19 x 33.5 in.; Scale: 200 ft. to 1 in.; Media: Manuscript map on linen paper.; Sheets: 1. (Othertype 755.48 S8 1836 & 1843 1897)
  - Map of the Lands of John Horsley Dec'd (now J. J. Bolton), at & near "Bolton Station," James River Div'n, C. & O. Ry., condemned by James River & Kanawha Company. Plotted from original condemnation papers. F. B. Isaacs, A. E., March. 1897., Dimensions: each 22.5 x 18 in.; Scale: 200 ft. to 1 in.; Media: Manuscript preliminary map.; Sheets: 2. (Othertype 755.48 S8 1897)
  - Map of Bolton Station on the James River Division; Ches. & Ohio R'y, showing also the Ches. & Ohio R'y Co.'s Lands, Tracks, etc., through the Farm of J. J. Bolton. Survey March 1897. Drawn April 1897 [by] F. B. Isaacs, A. E. See also 755.48/S8/1836 & 1843/1897; 755.48/S8/l897.., Dimensions: Copy 1, 26 x 36 in. Copy 2, 23.5 x 36 in. Copy 3, 23.25 x 35.5 in.; Scale: 200 ft. to 1 in.; Media: Manuscript colored plat. Copy 2, Manuscript colored tracing on linen paper. Copy 3, Blueprint of copy 1.; Sheets: 1 each. (Othertype 755.48 S8 1897 (1) copies 1-3)
  - Manchester Dam. October 1885., Dimensions: 24 x 31.5 in.; Scale: 100 ft. to 1 in.; Media: Manuscript map.; Sheets: 1. (Othertype 755.5 H9 1885)
  - Map showing James. River & Kanawha Water Power Co. from Bosher's Dam to Power House No.3. [Richmond, Va.] C. P. E. Burgwyn, Engineer in Charge. 1913., Dimensions: each 19 x 27.5 in. Part 31 is 12.5 x 26 in.; Media: Manuscript map in 31 parts.; Sheets: 9. (Othertype 755.5 H9 1913)
  - Right of Way and Track Map. The Chesapeake and Ohio Railway Company. James River Line. Ne1son County to Clifton Forge. June 30, 1916., Dimensions: each 24 x 18 in.; Scale: 200 ft. to 1 in.; Media: Blueline print.; Sheets: 79 sheets numbered 5, 6, 57 through 124, including supplementary sheets, in 238 parts. (Sheets numbered 1-4, 7 through 56 missing). (Othertype 755.5 S8 1916)
  - A map of that part of Judge William Daniel's Land taken for the use of the James River and Kanawha Co. [Lynchburg and Campbell County]. n.d.., Dimensions: 21 x 54 in.; Scale: 300 ft. to 1 in.; Media: Manuscript map. Colored.; Sheets: 1. (Othertype 755.5 S8 n.d.)
  - Richmond and Alleghany Railroad Map showing Manchester Canal. June 1883., Dimensions: 15 x 37 in.; Scale: 100 ft. to 1 in.; Media: Manuscript map. Colored.; Sheets: 1. (Othertype 755.57 R15 1883)
  - Manchester Canal and Adjacent Properties from actual survey, Sep. 1890. Additional notes made on March 6, 1893, and July 5, 1894. 1890-1894., Dimensions: each 29 x 19.5 in.; Scale: 50 ft. to 1 in.; Media: Blueprint map with additions in colored inks.; Sheets: 3. (Othertype 755.57 R15 1890 1893 & 1894)
  - C. & O. Ry. Co's. Land on the Manchester Canal, leased to the Marshall Manufacturing Co. Per Agreement Dated (January 1st, 1894). J. M. B. Lewis, Asst. Engr. June 1892. 1892-1894., Dimensions: 23 x 19.5 in.; Scale: Scale not given.; Media: Manuscript map. Colored.; Sheets: 1. (Othertype 755.57 R15 1892 1894)
  - Map of Land leased to Marshall Manufacturing Co. by Chesapeake & Ohio Railway Co. at Manchester, Virginia. F. B. Isaacs, A. E. March 1894., Dimensions: 17.5 x 23 in.; Scale: 30 ft. to 1 in.; Media: Manuscript map on linen paper.; Sheets: 1. (Othertype 755.57 R15 1894)
  - Profile of Buckingham Branch [Railroad]. June 1884., Dimensions: 9 x 27 in. and 9 x 28 in.; Scale: Scale not given.; Media: Manuscript profile. Colored.; Sheets: 2. (Othertype 755.576 R15 1884)
  - Map of Reusens Station & Canal Railway [Campbell County]. F. W. P. February 1901., Dimensions: each 17.5 x 26 in.; Scale: 100 ft. to 1 in.; Media: Manuscript map on linen paper.; Sheets: 2. (Othertype 755.584 C2 1901)
  - Map of Reusens Station & Canal on The Ches. & Ohio Railway [Campbell County]. F. B. Isaacs, Ertgr., W. P. February 1901., Dimensions: each 22 x 15 in.; Scale: Scale not given.; Media: Manuscript preliminary map.; Sheets: 2. (Othertype 755.584 R15 1901)
  - C. & O. Rt. of Way at Reusens [Campbell County]. n.d.., Dimensions: 10 x 36 in.; Scale: 200 ft. to 1 in.; Media: Manuscript map on linen paper.; Sheets: 1. (Othertype 755.584 R15 n.d.)
  - [Map of right of way at Reusen's, Campbell County]. n.d.., Dimensions: each 22 x 15 in.; Scale: Scale not given.; Media: Manuscript preliminary map.; Sheets: 2. (Othertype 755.584 R15 n.d. (1))
  - [Map of canal basin]. From Tracing of Daniels Hill, Lynchburg, Va. Dated 1875, & by E. S. Hunter. Dec. 11th, 1890. 1875-1890., Dimensions: 10 x 28 in.; Scale: Scale not given.; Media: Manuscript map on linen paper. Colored.; Sheets: 1. (Othertype 755.59 C2 1875 1890)
  - Lynchburg near Hurt's Mill. May 28, 1884. Traced from Drawing No. l15A, Nov. 9th, 1892. 1884-1892., Dimensions: 13 x 33 in.; Scale: 20 ft. to 1 in.; Media: Blueprint.; Sheets: 1. (Othertype 755.59 R15 1884 1892)
  - Map showing property of C. and O. Ry. at Lynchburg. Va. 1891., Dimensions: each 17 x 27 in.; Scale: 100 ft. to 1 in.; Media: }mnuscript map.; Sheets: 3. (Othertype 755.59 R15 1891)
  - Lynchburg, Va. Map showing location of 6 in. City [water main where it] crosses the property, canal, and tracks of [the Chesapeake and Ohio] Railway Co., etc. [1892]., Dimensions: 8 x 9.5 in.; Scale: Scale not given.; Media: Manuscript map.; Sheets: 1. (Othertype 755.59 R15 [1892])
  - Map of C. & O. Railway & Canal near Hurts Mills, Lynchburg, Va., showing C. S. & J. D. Langhorne's Lands. Surveyed by F. B. Isaacs, A. E. Oct. 3rd & 4th, 1895. 1895., Dimensions: 16 x 20 in.; Scale: 50 ft. to 1 in.; Media: Manuscript map. Colored.; Sheets: 1. (Othertype 755.59 R15 1895)
  - Map of C. & O. Railway & Canal near Hurt's Mills, Lynchburg, Va., showing C. S. & J. D. Langhorne's Lands. Surveyed by F. B. Isaacs, A. E. October 3 & 4, 1895. 1895., Dimensions: 12 x 20 in.; Scale: 50 ft. to 1 in.; Media: Manuscript map on linen paper.; Sheets: 1. (Othertype 755.59 R15 1895 (1))
  - Lynchburg, Va. map showing location of 6 in. City Water Main where it crosses the property, canal, & tracks of the Chesapeake & Ohio Railway Co. just below the corner of Jefferson and Washington Streets. F. B. Isaacs, A. E. May 1st, 1896.., Dimensions: 8 x 12 in.; Scale: Scale not given.; Media: Manuscript map on linen paper.; Sheets: 1. (Othertype 755.59 R15 1896)
  - Map of C. & O. Railway & Canal near Hurt's Mills, Lynchburg, Va. Surveyed and Drawn by F. B. Isaacs. 1897., Dimensions: 8 x 19 in.; Scale: 50 ft. to 1 in.; Media: Manuscript map on linen paper.; Sheets: 1. (Othertype 755.59 R15 1897)
  - Map No. 2. Map of the Land of the Chesapeake & Ohio Railway Co. at Lynchburg, Va., between Washington St. & Percival's Old Bridge. F. B. Isaacs, Engr. W. P.., Dimensions: 12 x 36 in.; Scale: 100 ft. to 1 in.; Media: Manuscript map on linen paper.; Sheets: 1. (Othertype 755.59 R15 1899)
  - Lynchburg. Plat of C. & O. Local Freight Depot and property acquired for Depot yard, and station purposes; making total frontage on Jefferson Street over 1400 feet. n.d.., Dimensions: 9 x 20 in.; Scale: 100 ft. to 1 in.; Media: Blueprint; Sheets: 1. (Othertype 755.59 R15 n.d.)
  - [Map of railroad and canal near Hurt's Mill, Lynchburg, Va.]. n.d.., Dimensions: 9 x 27 in.; Scale: 50 ft. to 1 in.; Media: Manuscript map on linen paper.; Sheets: 1. (Othertype 755.59 R15 n.d. (1))
  - C. & O. Ry. Craig Valley Branch [Botetourt and Craig counties] Right of Way. [1890?]., Dimensions: each 15 x 36 in., 29 x 36 in., 34 x 40 in.; Scale: (sheet 1) 400 ft. to 1 in, (sheets 2-20) 200 ft. to 1 in.; Media: Manuscript map. Colored.; Sheets: 20. (Othertype 755.7 R15 [1890?])
  - Warm Springs Branch [Alleghany and Bath counties]. Right of Way. [189l?]., Dimensions: each 18 x 36 in.; Scale: 200 ft. to 1 in.; Media: Manuscript map. Colored.; Sheets: 18. (Othertype 755.75 R15 [1891?])
  - [Right of way map of Richmond and Alleghany Railroad from Balcony Falls to Clifton Forge]. n.d.., Dimensions: 24 x 37 in.; Scale: Scale not given.; Media: Manuscript map. Colored.; Sheets: 61. (Othertype 755.72 R15 n.d.)
  - [Right of way map, Augusta County and Rockbridge County]. n.d.., Dimensions: each 27 x 40 in.; Scale: 200 ft. to 1 in.; Media: Manuscript map. Colored.; Sheets: 32 sheets numbered 116 through 149. (Othertype 755.72 S8 n.d.)
  - Waynesboro. M. A. Miller. [Shows railroad property and right of way for tracks]. 1880., Dimensions: each 20 x 24 in., except part 3, 20 x 20-1/2 in.; Scale: Scale not given.; Media: Manuscript map on linen paper. Colored.; Sheets: 3. (Othertype 755.78 R15 1880)
  - Copy of original map of Va. Central R. R., Covington Extension between Staunton & Swoops [Augusta County]. Original map ca. 1854. Copy ca. 1885. 1854-1885., Dimensions: each 25 x 38 in.; Scale: 200 ft. to 1 in.; Media: Manuscript plat of right of way. Colored.; Sheets: 2. (Othertype 755.78 S8 1854? 1885?)
  - Gravel Bank east of Waynesboro and line of C. & O. R. R. through the Land of J. J. Bell [Augusta County]. Aug. 6, 1877., Dimensions: 9 x 37 in.; Scale: 200 ft. to 1 in.; Media: Manuscript plat on linen paper. Colored.; Sheets: 1. (Othertype 755.78 S8 1877)
  - Swoope [Augusta County]. M. A. Miller. 1883., Dimensions: 12 x 28 in.; Scale: 100 ft. to 1 in.; Media: Manuscript plat on linen paper. Colored.; Sheets: 1. (Othertype 755.78 S8 1883)
  - [Map of right of way at Craigsville, Augusta County]. 1885?., Dimensions: 24 x 38 in.; Scale: 200 ft. to 1 in.; Media: Manuscript map.; Sheets: 1. (Othertype 755.78 S8 1885?)
  - [Plat showing right of way through land of David Bush in Waynesboro, Augusta County]. n.d.., Dimensions: 12 x 40 in.; Scale: 50 ft. to 1 in.; Media: Manuscript plat. Colored.; Sheets: 1. (Othertype 755.78 S8 n.d.)
  - Map of Agner's (Edmondson's) Dam and vicinity near 182-1/2 Mile Post, Lexington Branch, C. & O. Ry. J. M. B. Lewis, Asst. Engr. July 1892., Dimensions: each 17.5 x 28 in.; Scale: 30 ft. to 1 in.; Media: Manuscript map. Colored.; Sheets: 4. (Othertype 755.812 C2 1892)
  - Plat from Description in Deed between D[avid] Edmondson and North River Navigation Co. dated July 1852. Contents per deed, 7 acres 16 poles [Rockbridge County]: F. B. Isaacs. Feby. 1893., Dimensions: each 22 x 18 in.; Scale: 100 ft. to 1 in.; Media: Manuscript map.; Sheets: 2. (Othertype 755.812 C2 1893)
  - Plot of Land condemned on John Hogan for the use of the North River Improvement. September 5, 1895., Dimensions: 11 x 14.5 in.; Scale: Scale not given.; Media: Manuscript map on linen paper,; Sheets: 1. (Othertype 755.812 C2 1895)
  - Map of Agner's and Laird's Dams in Rockbridge Co. Va., made by J. M. B. Lewis. April 1896., Dimensions: 26 x 38 in.; Scale: 40 ft. to 1 in.; Media: Manuscript map.; Sheets: 1. (Othertype 755.812 C2 1896)
  - Map of Agner's and Laird's Dams in Rockbridge Co., Va., made by J. M. B. Lewis. April 1896., Dimensions: 26 x 38 in.; Scale: 40 ft. to 1 in.; Media: Blueprint.; Sheets: 1 per copy. (Othertype 755.812 C2 1896(1) copies 1 & 2)
  - [Map of Agner's Dam and vicinity, Rockbridge County]. [1896?]., Dimensions: 13.5 x 18 in.; Scale: 100 ft. to 1 in.; Media: Manuscript map on linen paper.; Sheets: 1. (Othertype 755.812 C2 1896?)
  - Agner's Dam [Rockbridge County]. Enlarged from Map with Condemnation from John Hogan's Heirs. February 28th, 1853., Dimensions: 13 x 31 in.; Scale: 100 ft. to 1 in.; Media: Manuscript map on linen paper.; Sheets: 1. (Othertype 755.812 C2 n.d.)
  - [Plat of property deeded by David Edmondson to North River Navigation Company, Rockbridge County, in July 1852]. July 1852., Dimensions: irregular.; Scale: Scale not given.; Media: Manuscript map on linen paper.; Sheets: 1. (Othertype 755.812 C2 n.d. (1))
  - Section of North River at a point about 700 ft. above N. & W. Bridge opposite Savernake. F. B. Isaacs, A. E. August 22nd, 1895., Dimensions: 10.5 x 28 in.; Scale: Scale not given.; Media: Manuscript profile.; Sheets: 1. (Othertype 755.812 H9 1895)
  - Sections of North River at a point about 800 ft. above N.& W. Bridge opposite Savernake. F. B. Isaacs, A. E. August 22nd 1895., Dimensions: 6.5 x 28 in.; Scale: Scale not given.; Media: Manuscript profile.; Sheets: 1. (Othertype 755.812 H9 1895 (1))
  - Map of C. & O. Ry. Co.'s Right of Way near 188 Mile Post, Lexington Branch, showing location of Bensalem Dam [Rockbridge County]. F. B. Isaacs, A. E. June 1892., Dimensions: 16 x 21 in.; Scale: 200 ft. to 1 in.; Media: Manuscript map on linen paper, colored.; Sheets: 1. (Othertype 755.812 R15 1892)
  - Map showing First Dam above Buena Vista (Rockbridge County), Va., and Buena Vista Paper Manufacturing Co's. Mill. F. B. Isaacs, Asst. Engr. March 12, 1892., Dimensions: 19.5 x 26.5 in.; Scale: 200 ft. to 1 in.; Media: Manuscript pre1iminary map.; Sheets: 1. (Othertype 755.812 R15 1892 (1))
  - Map showing First Dam above Buena Vista [Rockbridge County], Va., and Buena Vista Paper Manufacturing Co.'s Mil1. F. B. Isaacs, Asst. Engr. March 12, 1892., Dimensions: 10.5 x 24.5 in.; Scale: 200 ft. to 1 in.; Media: Manuscript map on linen paper.; Sheets: 1. (Othertype 755.812 R15 1892 (2))
  - Sketch of Ferry at Greenlee Station [Rockbridge County], James River Divn., C. & O. R'y. F. B. Isaacs, A. E. October 1897., Dimensions: 16 x 13 in.; Scale: 50 ft. to 1 in.; Media: Manuscript map on linen paper.; Sheets: 1. (Othertype 755.812 R15 1897)
  - [Sketch of ferry at Greenlee Station (Rockbridge County)]. F.B. Isaacs, A. E. October 1897., Dimensions: 23 x 15 in.; Scale: Scale not given.; Media: Manuscript map. Colored.; Sheets: 17. (Othertype 755.812 R15 1897 (1))
  - [Right of way map, Lexington Branch, from intersection of James River and North River thence up North River]. n.d.., Dimensions: 27 x 40 in.; Scale: Scale not given.; Media: Manuscript map. Colored.; Sheets: 17. (Othertype 755.812 R15 n.d.)